<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Minutes on UAPI group generic documents and meeting minutes</title><link>https://uapi-group.org/docs/minutes/</link><description>Recent content in Minutes on UAPI group generic documents and meeting minutes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://uapi-group.org/docs/minutes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://uapi-group.org/docs/minutes/2022-10-05__image-based-linux-summit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uapi-group.org/docs/minutes/2022-10-05__image-based-linux-summit/</guid><description>Image-based Linux summit, 5th - 6th October 2022, Berlin # The first image-based Linux summit took place on the 5th and the 6th of October, 2022. It was conducted as a loosely structured BoF-style event. The following parties were present at the summit (in no particular order):
Distros / Entities: Ubuntu Core, Debian, GNOME OS, Fedora CoreOS, Endless OS, Arch Linux, SUSE, Flatcar, Microsoft, Amazon, Meta Projects: systemd, image-builder/osbuild, mkosi, tpm2-software, System Transparency, buildstream, BTRFS, rpm-ostree Actionables and tasks # Action items listed here can be found as TODO #[x] in the full meeting minutes below, with [x] being the action item number.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://uapi-group.org/docs/minutes/2023-09-12__image-based-linux-summit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uapi-group.org/docs/minutes/2023-09-12__image-based-linux-summit/</guid><description>﻿Image-Based Linux Summit Berlin 12th September 2023 # Attendee&amp;rsquo;s projects # Systemd Meta: mkosi, systemd, remote attestation SUSE: Aeon/MicroOS/Tumbleweed Redhat: image-builder/osbuild, systemd, systemd-boot Microsoft: confidential containers, flatcar, Azure Boost, Mariner Edgeless Systems: Constellation, confidential containers NixOS: systemd-{repart,stub,boot,cryptenroll}, Tvix Store, Lanzaboote, UKIs, NixOS Bootspec,, PE binary manipulation in Rust Canonical: Ubuntu Core, snaps, foundations/bootloader/package management System Transparency: UKI, UAPI specs, systemd-cryptenroll, remote attestation, TPM eventlog, mkosi Amazon Linux Freedesktop-sdk GNOME OS carbonOS Summary of Last Year’s Progress # UAPI Group established Website!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://uapi-group.org/docs/minutes/2024-09-24__image-based-linux-summit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uapi-group.org/docs/minutes/2024-09-24__image-based-linux-summit/</guid><description>﻿Image-Based Linux Summit Berlin 24th September 2024 # Attendee&amp;rsquo;s projects # systemd mkosi SUSE: MicroOS/Tumbleweed Red Hat: image-builder/osbuild, bootc, systemd, systemd-boot Microsoft: confidential containers, Flatcar, Azure Boost, Mariner/Azure Linux Edgeless Systems: Constellation, Contrast (confidential containers), uplosi NixOS: systemd-{repart,stub,boot,cryptenroll}, tvix-store, Lanzaboote, UKIs, NixOS Bootspec, PE binary manipulation in Rust Canonical: Ubuntu Core, snaps, foundations/bootloader/package management System Transparency: UKI, UAPI specs, systemd-cryptenroll, remote attestation, TPM eventlog, mkosi Freedesktop-sdk GNOME OS Pengutronix: OE/Yocto, nspawn, RAUC, verity, OPTEE Arch Linux: sbctl/go-uefi, signstar, mkinitcpio, arch-install-scripts PostmarketOS Summary of Last Year’s Progress # Flatcar: Sysexts widely adopted: In-system (shipped with OS), optional but system dependent (updated in lock-step with OS, like podman/ZFS), Custom / user provided (updated from custom servers via sysupdate) Composable OS is more flexible, some traction with contributors, even vendors (Akamai) Mutable sysexts feature available in systemd-256 and newer.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://uapi-group.org/docs/minutes/2025-10-02__image-based-linux-summit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uapi-group.org/docs/minutes/2025-10-02__image-based-linux-summit/</guid><description>Image-Based Linux Summit Berlin October 2nd 2025 # 🖼️ 🐧 🗻 🥙
Attendee&amp;rsquo;s projects # systemd mkosi SUSE: MicroOS/Tumbleweed Red Hat: image-builder/osbuild, bootc, systemd, systemd-boot, composefs Fedora: Bootc, CoreOS, Atomic Desktops (Silverblue, Kinoite) Microsoft: confidential containers, Flatcar, Azure Boost NixOS: systemd-{repart,stub,boot,cryptenroll}, snix-store, Lanzaboote, UKIs, NixOS Bootspec, userborn, Sécurix Canonical: Ubuntu Core, snaps, foundations/bootloader/package management Freedesktop-sdk GNOME OS Arch Linux: sbctl/go-uefi, signstar(os), mkinitcpio, arch-install-scripts, devtools, buildbtw / vmexec, voa postmarketOS: mkosi and immutable images, dev tooling Devicetree selection for OS installers Cockpit https://github.</description></item></channel></rss>