<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Conferences on UAPI group generic documents and meeting minutes</title><link>https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/</link><description>Recent content in Conferences on UAPI group generic documents and meeting minutes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/2023-02-04__fosdem-devroom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/2023-02-04__fosdem-devroom/</guid><description>Image-Based Linux and Secure/Measured Boot Devroom @ FOSDEM 23 # The UAPI group, a community for people with an interest in innovating how we build, deploy, run, and update modern security-focused Linux operating systems, will host a devroom at FOSDEM 2023. A &amp;ldquo;devroom&amp;rdquo; (a FOSDEM term) is a co-located mini-conference with its own separate track.
FOSDEM is an annual free event for software developers to meet, share ideas and collaborate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/2023-02-05_fosdem-kernel-devroom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/2023-02-05_fosdem-kernel-devroom/</guid><description>Kernel Devroom @ FOSDEM 23 # We are pleased to announce the Call for Participation (CfP) for the FOSDEM 2023 Kernel Devroom.
FOSDEM 2023 will be over the weekend of the 4th and 5th of February in Brussels, Belgium. FOSDEM is a free and non-commercial event organised by the community for the community. The goal is to provide free and open source software developers and communities a place to meet to:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/2023-09-13__all-systems-go/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/2023-09-13__all-systems-go/</guid><description>All Systems Go! 2023 # All Systems Go! is a conference focused on foundational user-space Linux technologies. Its goal is to provide a gathering place for both contributors and users of projects that make up the foundation of modern Linux systems. The UAPI Group was well-represented with many speakers and related talks. Learn more at https://all-systems-go.io/
Talks abstracts and slide decks # Please see each individual talk on the schedule.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/2024-02-04_fosdem-kernel-devroom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/2024-02-04_fosdem-kernel-devroom/</guid><description>Kernel Devroom @ FOSDEM 24 # We are pleased to announce the Call for Participation (CfP) for the FOSDEM 2024 Kernel Devroom.
FOSDEM 2024 will be over the weekend of the 3rd and 4th of February in Brussels, Belgium. FOSDEM is a free and non-commercial event organised by the community for the community. The goal is to provide free and open source software developers and communities a place to meet to:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/2024-09-18__lpc-uapi-mc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uapi-group.org/docs/conferences/2024-09-18__lpc-uapi-mc/</guid><description>Kernel &amp;lt;-&amp;gt; Userspace/Init/System Management boundaries and APIs MicroConference @ LPC 24 # We are pleased to announce the Call for Participation (CfP) for the LPC 2024 Kernel &amp;lt;-&amp;gt; Userspace/Init/System Management boundaries and APIs MicroConference.
LPC 2024 will be held in Vienna, Austria, September 18th to 20th 2024.
The focus of this microconference will be on topics related to the APIs and interfaces sitting at the boundary between the kernel and init systems/system management layers, with a special attention directed towards current pain points and omissions.</description></item></channel></rss>